Guide to the Harold and Dorothy Seymour papers, 1830-2016
Seymour, Harold and Dorothy papers, 1830-2016
- RV Times, 1997 (Box 89, Folder 39)
- SASE Article, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 40)
- Curling for Encyclopedia, 1997-1999 (Box 89, Folder 41)
- Guest Appearance on Blue Ear, 1999-2003 (Box 89, Folder 42)
- Woman’s Work, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 43)
- Self-Publishing, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 44)
- Blue Ear, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 45)
- Publishing Success Writers’ Dig., 2000-2001 (Box 89, Folder 46)
- Articles in Naples News, 2000-2004 (Box 89, Folder 47)
- N Magazine, 2001 (Box 89, Folder 48)
- Museum Hopping, 2001-2002 (Box 89, Folder 49)
- Find Your Niche, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 50)
- A Woman’s Work, 2004-2005 (Box 89, Folder 51)
- Art Ideas Laby (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Artist (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Hallstat (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Austria 1930s, 1930s (Box 90, Folder 4)
- People: Hasburgs (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Prehistory (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Used in Labyrinth (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Berchtesgaden (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Europe 1930s, 1930s (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Labyrinth (Box 90, Folder 10)
- Mass Media in Austria (Box 90, Folder 11)
- Anschluss Part I (Box 90, Folder 12)
- Austria (Box 90, Folder 13)
- Hawaii (Box 90, Folder 14)
- Labyrinths (Box 90, Folder 15)
- Retirement Communities (Box 90, Folder 16)
- Lab (Box 90, Folder 17)
- Signs (Box 90, Folder 18)
- Labyrinth Materials, 2002 (Box 90, Folder 19)
- CDs for A Woman’s Work (Box 90, Folder 20)
- Permissions, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 21)
- A Woman’s Work Art (Box 90, Folder 22)
- Used and cited articles, 1990-2003 (Box 90, Folder 23)
- Articles Used in My Life, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 24)
- Province Articles, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 25)
- Used, 1989-2003 (Box 90, Folder 26)
- Notebook (Box 90, Folder 27)
- Jary Sell (Box 90, Folder 28)
- Pictures, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 29)
- Pictures Used (Box 90, Folder 30)
- Used in My Life, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 31)
- Pictures Not Used (Box 90, Folder 32)
- De Valera, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Kelts, 1998-1999 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Ireland, 1998-2000 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Kelts, 1999-2000 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- NYC-Italy, 2002-2004 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Italy, 2003-2004 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Italy-Sceptre, 2003-2004 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Ireland, 2003-2004 (Box 91, Folder 8)
- Ships etc., 2004 (Box 91, Folder 9)
- NYC, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 10)
- Italy, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 11)
- Italy and Hitler, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 12)
- Italy and Romans, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Italy, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 14)
- Italy and Romans, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 15)
- Italy, Hitler, 1930s, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 16)
- NY, Italy, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 17)
- Italy-Symbols, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 18)
- Kelts, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 19)
- NYC 1930s, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 20)
- Ireland History, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 21)
- Notes (Box 91, Folder 22)
- Postcards (Box 91, Folder 23)
- Notes and Pamphlets (Box 91, Folder 24)
- Spiral Notebooks (Box 91, Folder 25)
- Notebooks (Box 91, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous (Box 91, Folder 27)
- Research files for Drawing Card: A Baseball Novel (Box 92)
- Research files for Drawing Card: A Baseball Novel (Box 93, Folder 1-23)
- Research files for Chasing Baseball: Our Obsession With Its History, Numbers, People and Places (Box 93, Folder 24-36)
- Research files for Chasing Baseball: Our Obsession With Its History, Numbers, People and Places (Box 94)
- Hallowed Ground, 2000 Calendar of the 14 Greatest Ballparks, Folder in MS. Box 83
- Degrees, certificates, posters (Map-case Folder 1)
- Painting of a baseball match titled "American National Game of Base Ball, Grand Match for the Championship at the Elysian Fields, Hoboken NJ, 1865", 1865 (Map-case Folder 1)
- Photos of a China baseball team, 1878 (Map-case Folder 1)
- Copies of news articles about baseball, n.d. (Map-case Folder 1)
- Union Songs, Baseball, and Opera, tr-7188a